<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>@maksimkurb</title><link>https://cubly.ru/en/</link><description>Recent content on @maksimkurb</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ru-ru</language><copyright>Maxim Kurbatov</copyright><atom:link href="https://cubly.ru/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CV</title><link>https://cubly.ru/en/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cubly.ru/en/cv/</guid><description>Download resume in PDF format Maxim Kurbatov Java developer
Summary Have 3 years of experience in commercial development on the Spring stack with microservice architecture. Using all the power of Postgres, Kafka, and Hazelcast to build performant, scalable, and fault-tolerant systems. Previously worked with Node JS for about 2 years.
Contacts Telegram: @maksimkurb E-mail: max@cubly.ru Technical skills Industry Knowledge: Java, Spring Boot, JDBC, Hibernate, Kafka, JUnit, REST, WebSocket, Postgres, MySQL, Hazelcast, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Python, Redis, C# Technical Skills: IntelliJ IDEA, GitLab CI, Kubernetes, Maven, Gradle Soft skills: Communication, Problem Solving, Time Management, Mentoring, Teamwork Experience 08/2020 - now :: Java Developer, OneCell.</description><content>&lt;div style="max-width:400px;margin:0 auto">&lt;a href="../resume.pdf" target="_blank" class="button outline">Download resume in PDF format&lt;/a>&lt;/div>
&lt;h1 id="maxim-kurbatov">Maxim Kurbatov&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Java developer&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="summary">Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Have 3 years of experience in commercial development on the Spring stack with microservice architecture. Using all the power of Postgres, Kafka, and Hazelcast to build performant, scalable, and fault-tolerant systems. Previously worked with Node JS for about 2 years.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="contacts">Contacts&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;img src="../img/telegram.png" alt="telegram logo" class="inline"> Telegram: &lt;a href="https://t.me/maksimkurb">@maksimkurb&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;img src="../img/email.png" alt="email icon" class="inline"> E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:max@cubly.ru">max@cubly.ru&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="technical-skills">Technical skills&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Industry Knowledge&lt;/strong>: &lt;code>Java, Spring Boot, JDBC, Hibernate, Kafka, JUnit, REST, WebSocket, Postgres, MySQL, Hazelcast, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Python, Redis, C#&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Technical Skills&lt;/strong>: &lt;code>IntelliJ IDEA, GitLab CI, Kubernetes, Maven, Gradle&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Soft skills&lt;/strong>: &lt;code>Communication, Problem Solving, Time Management, Mentoring, Teamwork&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="experience">Experience&lt;/h2>
&lt;!-- =================== -->
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>08/2020 - now :: Java Developer, OneCell.ai&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>OneCell.ai is a digital pathology platform, with AI-system, scanning hardware and smart storage that helps to save lives.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Acheivements:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Designed/developed the MVP of the platform backend in 2 months&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Split a huge monorepo with modules into 10 independent repositories to enable separate versioning of microservices
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Used GIT history rewriting tools&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mentored and coached 3 colleagues on the team&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved the workspace in Notion to make it easier for the whole team to work with their own tasks&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Technologies:&lt;/strong>
&lt;em>Java, Spring, Spring Boot, Kafka, Postgres, Hazelcast, WebSockets, JUnit, MinIO, tus.io, libVIPS, Python&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- =================== -->
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>09/2019 - 02/2020 :: Intern Java Developer, Grid Dynamics International, Inc&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Development of a batch system that accumulates customer data from various sources, processes it and provides it to other systems.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Responsibilities:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Backend development (Technical design, Development, Code review, Creating test cases)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Prepare demo-scripts and show demo&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Scrum methodology&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Technologies:&lt;/strong>
&lt;em>Java, Spring, Spring Boot, Kafka, MySQL, Maxwell, Spring Batch, Google Cloud Platform&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- =================== -->
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>2017 – 06/2018, 12/2018 - 08/2019 :: Full Stack developer&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>System for checking individuals and legal entities for risk factors. The system aggregates information from various sources and generates reports by operator request, consisting of real-time APIs and APIs with queue processing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Responsibilities:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Backend development (GraphQL API, Third-party service integration, Billing service integration, Documenting, OAuth provider implementation)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Frontend development (Personal profile page on backend, React Native App for making queries)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Technologies:&lt;/strong>
&lt;em>NestJS, GraphQL, Redis, Queues, Postgres, TypeScript, React, React Native, Jenkins, Jest&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- =================== -->
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>09/2018 – 11/2018 :: Frontend Developer, LIS Ltd&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>CRM for construction companies&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Responsibilities:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Frontend development (Web app on React stack)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Setting up Continuous Integration&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Working with Kanban methodology&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Technologies:&lt;/strong>
&lt;em>React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Reselect, Jest, NodeJS, Webpack, FeathersJS, Immutable JS, Git, Gitlab CI, Postman, Json, Shell&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- =================== -->
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>2017 :: Individual project development&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Timetable for school lecture with website for filling schedule (with ability to importing from Dnevnik.ru) and Android app with widget&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Technologies:&lt;/strong>
&lt;em>Meteor, Android, Java, REST, FullCalendar.js, xlsx parsing&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- =================== -->
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>2016 :: Sartax.ru&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Interactive map (using Google Maps) with taxi drivers, their prices and total calculation. Also has panel for taxi drivers with taxi meter and GPS location tracker.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Technologies:&lt;/strong>
&lt;em>PHP, REST, Laravel, JavaScript, Bootstrap, GPS, Google Maps&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="education-and-certificates">Education and Certificates&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>2022-2023, Infocommunications and digital media, ITMO University&lt;/li>
&lt;li>2017-2021, Computer Science and Computer Engineering, Saratov State Technical University&lt;/li>
&lt;li>2020, Aptech Certified Software Technology Specialist
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Certificate in Programming - CREDIT&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Diploma in Programming - DISTINCTION&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Advanced Diploma in Enterprise Applications - Java - DISTINCTION&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>2019, Web Development with Java and Spring, GridU&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="languages">Languages&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>English - B2&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Russian - native speaker&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;a style="margin-top:2em" href="../resume.pdf" target="_blank" class="button primary">Download resume in PDF format&lt;/a>&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>No posts has been translated to English yet :(</title><link>https://cubly.ru/en/posts/0-no-posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cubly.ru/en/posts/0-no-posts/</guid><description>Try browsing Russian version of this site instead
.. or checkout my CV</description><content>&lt;p>Try browsing &lt;a href="../">Russian version&lt;/a> of this site instead&lt;/p>
&lt;p>.. or checkout my &lt;a href="../en/cv">CV&lt;/a>&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>